Narrator: Part 2
Host: OK, Team B.
You have one minute to ask Team A questions.
George: Hmm… let’s start with Nadine.
Mike’s your hair stylist, right?
Nadine: Yes, we’re very good friends.
George: What’s the name of his salon?
Nadine: Uh, it’s called… uh… Good Hair Day.
Charlie: Is Mike married?
Nadine: Uh, yes, he is.
Alice: Does he have children?
Nadine: Uh, yes, uh… no, he doesn’t.
I don’t think he has children.
Alice: OK, so now, Tyler.
You say Mike’s your dentist.
Where is his office?
Tyler: It’s, uh, downtown, near the shopping mall.
Charlie: Are you and Mike friends?
Tyler: Well, no, not really friends.
It’s difficult to be friends with your dentist –
it’s impossible to have a conversation!
George: Is he expensive?
Tyler: What do you think?
He’s a dentist!
George: OK, James now.
You say Mike’s a chef in a restaurant.
What’s the name of the restaurant?
James: The Red Lion.
It’s a great restaurant.
Charlie: What food does Mike cook?
James: Uh, great French food!
French onion soup, steak frites, things like that.
And he makes good crepes.
Alice: What’s his specialty?
James: Uh, spaghetti carbonara.
Host: OK, team.
Your time’s up.